In this video we create extension about curses
Because for example if you recorded any cards or any videos, sometimes you want to hide some an element of or blur it out
So there are some extensions that we can actually see how it works. For example, hide that it will hide the element
Click to remove an element, if you remove an element. There's a hover zoom
So you just create like on favorite websites and simply hover mouse over to use it
There is a smooth zoom
so we can actually
Press some of the buttons and this is application like hide since if you're matching the in-life
Do screen sharing and it's possible to even monetize it because yeah, we have a possibility to
Use a zoom in. So me allows us to
zoom some of them
Information that you have sometimes in the courses, so this way and we can actually create
You can start from the simple functionality first our open folder
It will be called Kerz Assistant
I'll use maybe one of the articles from outrest
I have this element if I press hide that it's basically hiding
That's great
And if I refresh probably to re-appear again
So it's just for preparation, but there is even extension click to remove element
So if I go here
Let me refresh it and I have a click to remove element
It will be brought with the mark so now I can extend it as you can see it's now
Actually, I'm refreshed so it's perfect
We can even remember if I set to remember and refresh it
As you can see it's actually saved I'll give from here
So if you remember is that some of the
Remove element is a little bit better. We see it in the
window and obviously we can try to add another tab and another thing, but yeah, this way we can easily
Save some of the status this pretty simple because it just hides this one hides and remember the information
So if I have this I have this I can remember and then refresh and
Yeah, now if I press the game
You can preview the elements that were hidden before
So if we do our first functionality, we know what we can do now
I want to create
Notice maybe make it in the total list in the plan
I want to create a modern Chrome extension
That will allow us to
hide elements on the website
This website
This options should include
Saving
Hidden elements where we want to reload the page
Or just one time
When we don't want it to be hidden when we reloads
Edge again
Okay, so this is the one simple thing, but hopefully I want to show some of the designs
Because I pretty much like the design, but I would like to have it like similar to it
So I'll just can copy
You
I'll paste it
They can inspiration in this
But make it as a it returns it changes the icon this another window that will be displayed
I
Okay
And there
Come extension
I come
And it should be
Compactors
And the thing
Another thing is to quick hide elements
We write mouse but I'm a context
menu
That will automatically
Add an entry to that window if you want
To have advanced features
Like remember hidden elements
And preview hidden elements
If element was hidden and saved
The half icon of Chrome
Should display
Counter
None of elements that are
Hidden safety
We'll now see the result
You
It's not because we have a preview even all the thing. I think I don't need this because
I'm not a colder so and I can always inspect right with any website and see it
So I don't need this
So I would just probably simplify if I x okay, it's back and now
This is the remote by default. I can remove this we will return
And we'll see the result on now we have elements
So it's still planning a thing
First should elements be removed from the DOM or hidden
And that's a good question because I'm not sure which one is there
As I think a display none will be all right
Hmm
Remember scope now we'll ask him
What is the difference between
Don't or hidden
Says this and how is it handled in popular
Chrome extensions like
Quick to remove element
Okay, so just first ask
Will you CSS how we answer it to it and you CSS
Now we can have a
Member scope
Should be
Specific URL but we can actually check it for example
We have a hide element
There is out with if I type it and hide it and save it
If every load it's not showing with we go to academy
We see by default it's handling it's handling given the different one
So even in articles now if I press it
And review it's
Actually saving the whole and I think it's worth too much we can actually add the option but remember
scope not per specific URL but
Per domain all pages, okay
Preview feature when previewing a hidden element should temporarily show toggle visibility highlights
Okay, temporary show
It's it's correct
And temporary show
For preview feature when we test a hidden element
And now we can see patch counter should be shown count from the current page on the dot how count across all safety then
I need only account or current page
I
Now I would just ask don't create icons remove icons reference for now because I want to test it
So now it would just work with default icon now an extension and I consider
Okay, I will press escape and now I will add this as a Chrome extension
our load impact
And I will use course assistant
Element hi there, so just to take the name for itself and now I can I read here
So we see hidden elements here all trust
We don't right-click and hide element here. So if we go to main page
Maybe releases
Go to articles to the article and I will press this element. So I have a hi dad hide element
And unfortunately enough in case working
So our height element is not shown right now to hide it so
You probably have to add something
Open agent mode now open you one
Head element is not working
Please
exit
And I press hide element
Maybe we can change
Subcategory
to hide and blur
So it will be easier and then by clicking on extension icon
You should have a list of blurred
hidden elements and
switch
Pretty room
Between them
Now it's done improving hidden elements now to my page
And now I can press it
First of all just refresh
See there was an error even have a clear all and if just error still exists. I will just try to use it
So now hide that
Hide blur element
So I can say blur
Doesn't work
Change my name to change visibility
And then add
Then
Allow us to use hide
show
I hide blur
And please try to
Check why blurring or hiding
Element is
Not working when I press it
I didn't have an extension error, but now let me see so I have a manage visibility height once
Okay, I think it's working now even if I don't see anything. It's just
Manage persistent. It shows that actually but the element of the child
If I try it again and now probably I won't hide this element because now obviously if I press hide that
It will show
But now I will use a game manage visibility
And I would say hide once
Okay, so actually it started to work just problem with the picker
So if I use now blur once, okay, that's perfect. So now we are doing something. I'm happy with it
and
Still
With the persistent we could probably add the elements that are hidden. I see if I press it now and
Use manage visibility and blur persistent it will add and when I refresh it
Yeah, it works again and we can use preview to sit for my case
Even when I use the manage visibility and hide once I would like to get possibility to still be able to
Turn it off. For example, I don't want to reload it again. I think it will be nice. I'll go again to Chrome extension
That's perfect
Although
the cool base situation
When I mark something
It will be hidden for blur once but then want to reload
but then want to
Review visible thing
Without so the one time
Is ready
We see update now if I go back again
refer the page press
manage visibility hide once
We still don't have an option
If I refresh it and not sure I would me go again
Hide once
What I mean by that I want to get
From vacation and possibility to change visibility
Even if it was just hidden or blurred
Once and we can even check other things to add more features
That's actually nice feature to masking taxi faster. It's
How I did
We see extension now
our refresh hide once
We see it's now here, but we didn't see a notification so for now we can just
Add this one thing. It works nearly perfect
Just add that notification
Red one on how you come
from extension
Open your agent and add in your feature
So the new feature will be and like we saw on the Google
Some extensions allow it to just for multiple effects
So just burn it with some masking texts with their
I want you to implement this
and
Astor is
for text
and
truth
another effect the handler
hide
And it adds possibility
so you'll just plan the new move
Have a possibility to manage visibility element hider
But we can add
functionality to mark the element that we can hide once or twice so
Think it will be nice to use it
So use the Chrome extension again. I use your agent
another feature
I would like to have
Easiest, least, least, least, with it
I'm going to
choose a part of the page
Rectangle with a picture that will be hidden or blurred
Tell that one, okay
It should probably implement an icon. So just press the game
Now I have a masking effects. Wow
It was very quick. So now we have a mask resistant redact ones covers and I'm going to be solid back over
We have a possibility of reduction effects or icons
It's done. Now just refresh. Actually, we had a lot of things. Oh, we see some errors. We see, okay
Thank you. Rome. You can even type message. So quickly fix it. Thank you
I don't want this
so
I can't select
I will refresh to it. Please
remove all of the
references
latest to icons because I'm just testing
Instantly, I'm just marking on files. I just can't implement it in code
I wish it could add something to a code, but okay, we see it
Oh, now it's just some incandence. We have a better count
Some requests taking a close it
Open the hierarchy directly from here
So we have all of the types redact resistant
And yeah, remove the renaming batches
Okay, now refresh it
I think now should work and now when I go back
My manager visibility have more things as we can see
Mark once with asterisks
Mark persistent
So this one will not work with this element will work
This one will not probably have it. So the text should be only detected by the element
And we can easily make it now in this redact one. So it's
The stat that we are marking. So if I use this now
Mark it down a redact one it will detect
And but still we don't have this that area picker. I will text it soon
I will refresh it
Redact
And
Asterates should be only
visible when we
Marked text and same for images
These options should be visible when elements
It's not a text
Use text as a branch
To switch
This visibility
And
For one time application
I don't see
And notification icon
Okay
Call for you now it returned to the previous stage
And I'm in hider and if I press text manage visibility
Asterix ones
Okay, we see it's visible now
Oh, it's now even a working
So
Blue ones. It's now working. That's perfect
I was scared of it that I would have to do the video again
But luckily
Now it's working. But we see the sometimes when you apply it to effects
It still doesn't show so we'll add a small feature now
When I apply
Blur and hidden
Or hidden and burr
It should remove previous
Visibility because when I turn off
Again
I cannot
Return to defaults visible to the state
And another feature will be um
I think it will be the last one because this video is really long
But you probably have can implement a lot of things
and
Have my hero the visibility and once in my main window to have
Think like because for example if I read it once if you just press press bottom
So I can press press
Blur intensity and react so as new agent
The main from extension window
Add settings
Adjust blur
Intensity and red-act color
Okay, this should probably work by default because it will just change if the current display is none and start this page none
I'll add settings for blur and redact
Stining
So we have here
Do try to handle settings in a pop-up JavaScript file
The background homework function to your settings
I
All right, as we can see it's now finished now just refresh it those still some
I don't know that I'm not sure
Okay, it's not working
And now if I go to my high-development C blur intensity now if I use this trying to manage with the load here like a
Hide once
Let me not try once. I will just
Remove it and I will just use this extension
Make this and I will use the blur ones
It says blur, but by default I think
It's not showing so just use the full blur
Okay, so it works, but the blur density
Yeah, now it's working so we can adjust
Think the 10 is just what wasn't refreshing now and if I press a redact color
You have a black thing, but see if I press like this
It automatically changes
Okay, so this way we can do it and obviously we can remove it now not just visibility